Hi.
This is Willy.
Willy is going to help me demonstrate the Yoga Kiss.
Willy is seated in dandawson, lengthening from the tailbone to the crown of the head.
He's squeezing through his thighs, pulling his calves into his shins, pressing through his heels and pulling his toes back towards his knees.
He's going to bend his knees, and bring his heels out a little bit wider than his hips.
Good.
He's going to inhale and reach his arms forward, and he's going to take them around and place them on the ground underneath his legs.
He's going to try to pull his bellybutton in lengthen through his spine, and he's going to lift his legs up, finding that perfect point of balance.
Good.
Then he's going to bring his heels together for the kiss, and notice that his hands are in guion mudra.
The thumb represents the universe.
The forefinger represents the chi line, or energy line, that runs from the tip of the finger all the way to his heart.
Thereby connecting Willy's heart to the heart of the universe.
Very nice.
He's going to release this pose, releasing his hands, taking his feet down, extending his legs back out into his dendawsama.
And that was the Yoga Kiss.